Nicole to me is kinda of being unique
and being someone who you want to be
and like how you see yourself ,I guess
She says they're walking in a straight line
But that's not really her style
They all got the same heartbeat
But hers is falling behind
Nothing in this world could
Ever bring them down
Yeah, they're invincible
And she's just in the background
And she says
I wish that I could be like the cool kids
'Cause all the cool kids
They seem to fit in
I wish that I could be like the cool kids
Like the cool kids
He says I'm talking with a big smile
But they haven't got a clue
Yeah, they're living the good life
Can't see what he is going through
They're driving fast cars
But they don't know where they're going
In the fast lane
Living life without knowing
And he says
I wish that I could be like the cool kids
'Cause all the cool kids
They seem to fit in
I wish that I could be like the cool kids
Like the cool kids
'Cause all the cool kids
They seem to get it
I wish that I could be like the cool kids
Like the cool kids
And they said
I wish that I could be like the cool kids
'Cause all the cool kids
They seem to fit in
I wish that I could be like the cool kids
Like the cool kids
'Cause all the cool kids
They seem to fit in
I wish that I could be like the cool kids
Like the cool kids
'Cause all the cool kids
They seem to get it
I wish that I could be like the cool kids
Like the cool kids